<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-11-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>First Post</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/2014/11/21/First-Post.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/2014/11/21/First-Post.html</id>
    <published>2014-11-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2014-11-23T05:16:27+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Since June of this year, I've been attempting to learn web development through books and online resources. I'v read &lt;em&gt;Apprenticeship Patterns&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Why’s (Poignant) Guide to Ruby&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Learn Python the Hard Way&lt;/em&gt;, and many other books.  I've tried &lt;a href="https://www.codeschool.com/"&gt;codeschool&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.codecademy.com/"&gt;codeacademy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://teamtreehouse.com/"&gt;treehouse&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.codewars.com/"&gt;codewars&lt;/a&gt; and an assortment of other sites posting tutorials. I've signed up for email newsletters, added blogs to my rss reader, and listened to at least a dozen different podcast. And after all that, I still feel like a beginner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started this, I was thinking of picking up a few skills to add to my resume. Another way to make myself more employable. As a college dropout, I didn't see many options for myself and I couldn't bring myself to go back to school without a clear plan. The past few years before then left such a bad taste in my mouth that I was striving for a complete do over. So many of my peers were talking about their passion and I didn't feel like I had one.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went through several rabbit holes and I found myself doing the web design coruse track at treehouse. Once coding came into the picture, I was hooked. At first, I didn't know what I found so appealing about it. I just remember thinking about how amazing it was to create a website. Following through from design to user interactions to user authentication. Half of things I saw didn't make sense but I took a little bit of what did and stored it in my brain. I went through multiple course tracks trying to absorb as much information as I can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The past few months have been like solving a jigsaw puzzle. I take the pieces I find along the way and try to piece it together. Sometimes I can see the bigger picture and sometimes I don't but the pieces themselves feel like precious gemstones waiting to be cut, polished and presented someday. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog will be about that. I'll try to make sense of what I found and pick up more things along the way. Also, after further thinking, I've decided to ammend that first paragraph. I'm an advanced beginner trying to get to intermediate. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
